Privacy Policy
==============

**1\. Information Collection and Use**

WebExtension.ORG will not collect any personally identifiable information about You - such as your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address - unless You provide it to WebExtension.ORG voluntarily and approve its use.

If you do not want your personally identifiable information collected, please do not submit it to WebExtension.ORG. If you contribute personally identifiable information to WebExtension.ORG, it may use such information to better understand your requirements and how it may enhance its products and services. WebExtension.ORG may also use that information to contact You, for example, to answer a question or respond to a comment You have submitted. WebExtension.ORG maintains the right to publish on our website any queries or comments you make, along with any reply provided by WebExtension.ORG, without identifying you (i.e. discussion section). WebExtension.ORG will use your information to analyze your request, authenticate your identity and the identities of your other project participants, and for any other legitimate objectives related to your request in the event of requests for new pages. It will not, however, share your information with third parties without your permission, unless it is compelled by law, as detailed below in the "Information Sharing" section.

WebExtension.ORG may gather information that is not individually identifiable in some situations. The type of the Internet browser or computer operating system you use, the date and time you visited the site, the pages you browsed, and the name of the website from which you linked to the site are all examples of this sort of information. This data is used by WebExtension.ORG to study trends and compile broad demographic data for aggregate usage. There is no relationship between this data and any personally identifying information.

This website is an open-source site and the data and information posted on the site are publically accessible by design. Anonymous messages (or posts that have been edited to be made anonymous) are against the spirit of open source. When You offer content for other WebExtension.ORG users to read, attaching your name to it gives other WebExtension.ORG users the ability to reply to You privately about it, in case they feel that a public reply would be inappropriate. If You want to avoid spam, use mail filters, or refrain from posting on the Site. WebExtension.ORG will not be responsible for any unsolicited email that You receive as a result of You posting your email address on the newsgroups, chat rooms, or mailing lists.

**2\. Cookies**

WebExtension.ORG may use cookies on the Site. This information will be in the form of a cookie or similar file and will help WebExtension.ORG enhances its web experience by saving time on the Site. This can also make your next visit easier and the site more useful to you. In general, cookies play an important role. Without them, using the web would be a much more frustrating experience. With most Internet browsers, you can easily erase cookies from your computer's hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However, these may stop our website from functioning properly. Please refer to your browser instructions or "help" screen to learn more about these functions.

WebExtension.ORG may use cookies for the following reasons.

a. WebExtension.ORG allows you to share pages with some social networks such as Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Google Plus, Pinterest, and Stumbleupon. Each of these networks has its cookie policy. Please visit each social media website to see their cookie policies before sharing any content.

b. We also use Google Analytics and Google AdSense on the WebExtension.ORG website. Google uses certain cookies to better operate on third-party websites. Please refer to Google's [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy), page to get more info.

c. WebExtension.ORG uses Cloudflare services such as CDN. Cloudflare has certain cookie policies regarding its services. To read more about Cloudflare's cookie policy please visit Cloudflare.com [Privacy Policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/).

**3\. Information Sharing**

Although WebExtension.ORG makes every effort to preserve user privacy, it may need to disclose information when required by law wherein it has a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order, or legal process served on the Site.

**4\. Security**

The Site has security procedures in place to safeguard the information within WebExtension.ORG's control from loss, misuse, and modification. However, because a sufficiently strong assault from an unauthorized third party might compromise your data, it is impossible to ensure the security or integrity of the information you share online.

**5\. Links to None-WebExtension.ORG Sites**

The Site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that WebExtension.ORG is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. WebExtension.ORG encourages You to be aware when You leave the Site and to read the privacy statements of every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the Site.

**6\. How to Contact WebExtension.ORG**

If You have any questions or suggestions regarding WebExtension.ORG's privacy policy, please send an email to [\[email protected\]](https://webextension.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
